Guide to the Mid-Hudson Valley Transgender Association records, 1970-2014.
Mid-Hudson Valley Transgender Association records
- Series VI. Media
  - DVDs
    - No Dumb Questions, 2001-06-21; DVD-1910
      Epiphany Productions
    - Let Me Die a Woman, 1977; DVD-1911
      Hygiene Films
    - Cruel and Unusual: Transgender Women in Prison, 2006-10-24; DVD-1912
      Reid Productions
    - The Montel Williams Show: "Transgendered: A Struggle For Acceptance", 2007; DVD-1913
      Mountain Movers Inc.
    - Donna Rose: Transgender in the Workplace, 2005-08; DVD-1914 (Box 2)
      Rochester, New York
    - All My Children, undated; DVD-1915
    - Unraveling Michelle, 2008-03-10; DVD-1916 (Box 2)
      Absolute Independent Pictures
    - The Dr. Keith Ablow Show: Helen & Betty, 2007-02; DVD-1917
      Telepictures Productions
    - Helen & Betty, 2007-06-25; DVD-1918
      Mid-Hudson Valley Transgender Association
    - 100% Woman, 2004; DVD-1919
      Artemis Dreams Productions
    - Born a Boy, Brought up a Girl, 2009; DVD-1920
      TLC
    - 20/20: "My Secret Self", 2007-04-27; DVD-1921-1922
    - Screaming Queens: The Riot at Compton's Cafeteria, 2005-06-18; DVD-1923
      PBS
    - The Opposite Sex: Jamie's Story, 2004-06-07; DVD-1924
      Krasnow Productions
    - Beautiful Daughters, 2006-02-11; DVD-1925
      Aronson Films Production
    - 48 Hours Investigates: "Trapped", 2004-02-25; DVD-1926
      CBS News
    - Second Serve: The Renee Richards Story, 1986-05-13; DVD-1927
      Lorimar Telepictures
    - The Tyra Banks Show: “We’re 7 & 8 Years Old and Know We Are Transgender”, 2010-01; DVD-1928
      The CW Network
    - The Adventures of Sebastian Cole, 1999-01-23; DVD-1929
      Culpan Productions LLC
    - CSI: "Ch-ch-changes", 2004-11-18; DVD-1930
      Jerry Bruckheimer Television
    - Paul Zahu Now Transgender Gay Cure, 2007-06-27; DVD-1931
      CNN
    - At War with the Army, 1951-01-17; DVD-1932 (Box 2)
      Fred F. Finklehoffe Productions
    - Voice Program Exercises, undated; DVD-1933-1934
      Deep Stealth Productions
    - Joann Prinzivalli @ Transgender Issues, undated; DVD-1935
    - The Adventures of Priscilla, Queen of the Desert, 1994-08-10
      Collection included empty DVD case which has been removed.
      PolyGram Filmed Entertainment
  - CDs
    - DJ's PIX / New Paltz Parade, 2005-06; CD-3230
    - NYCTR Gender Presentation, 2013-03; CD-3231
      New York Citizens for Transgender Rights; New York
    - Janice in Provincetown & San Francisco, undated; CD-3232
      Provincetown, Massachusetts | San Francisco, California
    - Janice with Marcie, undated; CD-3233
    - Cosmopolitan Virtual Makeover 3, 2000; CD-3234 (Box 2)
      Mattel Interactive; Hearst Communications, Inc.
    - Transgender Community News, 1999-01 - 2001-12; CD-3235-3237
      Renaissance Transgender Association, Inc.
- Series VII. Miscellaneous
  - Transgender Umbrella Graphic, undated; Reiff Hill, Mel (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Image adapted from Josephine Tittsworth by Mel Reiff Hall
  - "The Rose" Poem, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Question Gender Graphic, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Halloween Hints, 1997; Kamentsky, Gina (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Printed September 25, 2001
  - Picture Printouts, 1998 - 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Integrated Product Development, 1998-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Douglas Archer File, 1998-10 - 1999-02 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Combined Gender Identity and Transsexuality Inventory Results (COGIATI), 2000-05-22 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Seattle Post-Intelligencer Comic, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Seattle, Washington
  - Holiday Songs Final Exam, 2003-12-10 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Humor Matters
  - Movie Monologues, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Notebook, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Death Announcements, 2014-10 - 2014-11 (Box 2, Folder 41)